<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prashant Khurana</title>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prashant Khurana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sync between Google drive and dropbox using rclone</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/rclone-copy-drive-dropbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/rclone-copy-drive-dropbox/</guid>
      <description>Rclone is a command line program to sync files and directories to and from various cloud service providers.
Among others, it supports Google Drive, Dropbox, Amazon Drive, Box, Microsoft One Drive, Yandex and Backblaze. An exhaustive list can be found over here.
This is a mental dump of how to setup rclone and sync between dropbox and google drive. I generally store my files in Google drive and then once a month sync them over to dropbox and backblaze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Learn Part 2</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/learning-how-to-learn-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/learning-how-to-learn-2/</guid>
      <description>I recently enrolled myself in &amp;lsquo;Learning how to Learn&amp;rsquo; course on coursera. Part 1 of this series listed my motivations for doing so, and summary of week 1 of the course.
Before summarizing my learnings from week 2, I would like to go over the things that have stuck with me from week 1. These techniques have passed the test of time(a month, hah) :
 Pomodoro Technique : I have found this to be very effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Learn Part 1</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/learning-how-to-learn-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 16:52:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/learning-how-to-learn-1/</guid>
      <description>Recently I decided to take one of the most popular courses on Coursera : Learning how to learn.
Motivation I had been trying to go over deep learning course on fast.ai and somehow I was not making progress and hence started to procrastinate. In retrospect there are a few reasons I can think of, as to why I gave up on the course(for the time being) :
 I decided to deep dive into it and thought that I can do a quick glance of the course in a few weeks whereas the recommended time to finish the course is 3 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/rclone-copy-drive-dropbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/rclone-copy-drive-dropbox/</guid>
      <description>Sync between Google drive and dropbox using rclone  /** * prism.js Github theme based on GitHub&#39;s theme. * @author Sam Clarke */ code[class*=&#34;language-&#34;], pre[class*=&#34;language-&#34;] { color: #333; background: none; font-family: Consolas, &#34;Liberation Mono&#34;, Menlo, Courier, monospace; text-align: left; white-space: pre; word-spacing: normal; word-break: normal; word-wrap: normal; line-height: 1.4; -moz-tab-size: 8; -o-tab-size: 8; tab-size: 8; -webkit-hyphens: none; -moz-hyphens: none; -ms-hyphens: none; hyphens: none; } /* Code blocks */ pre[class*=&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>http://example.com/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/presentations/</guid>
      <description>In the last few years I gave a bunch of presentations. This is a collection of those. At the time, I was not focussing on publishing them, so some of the content would be missing as I did not document everything. Feel free to contact me if anything piques your interest.
1) Rust presentation with focus on differentiating features of rust ie. owenership, borrowing and lifetimes. Github Link
2) Graph Databases : Neo4j.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>